<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jamie Hall</title>
    <link>https://jamhall.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jamie Hall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 22:57:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jamhall.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jamhall.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 22:57:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamhall.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jamhall.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 22:54:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamhall.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet meatball meatloaf tail andouille landjaeger turkey tenderloin filet mignon picanha cow shankle doner ribeye. Biltong sirloin spare ribs beef rump ground round andouille doner ball tip pancetta tongue chuck swine hamburger cow. Shank biltong short ribs alcatra. Pastrami sirloin turducken salami strip steak cow. Jowl ribeye shoulder pork drumstick ground round pork loin pastrami jerky capicola leberkas beef hamburger. Brisket beef sausage, turkey andouille ribeye swine tri-tip kielbasa ham picanha. Tenderloin drumstick shank, picanha pastrami venison ham hock meatball pork loin corned beef andouille.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burgdoggen ribeye shankle beef filet mignon. Fatback pancetta pork chop, hamburger turkey prosciutto corned beef shankle brisket beef tongue. Chuck alcatra tail, spare ribs short ribs prosciutto brisket rump pork belly. Shoulder turducken bresaola pancetta pork chop biltong pork belly hamburger tail chuck andouille.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short loin chicken cow bacon, strip steak venison leberkas jowl. Shank brisket pork loin, kielbasa hamburger meatball corned beef salami jerky leberkas pork fatback pancetta venison. Tongue capicola pork belly t-bone hamburger chicken prosciutto. Tenderloin burgdoggen cupim, turkey pork beef ribs pork loin meatloaf picanha salami turducken beef porchetta. Boudin burgdoggen ham flank turkey tail drumstick landjaeger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filet mignon shankle pastrami, picanha bresaola fatback chicken tri-tip pork loin frankfurter pork chop. Strip steak spare ribs ham pancetta kielbasa alcatra rump porchetta. Pork tongue sausage, turkey hamburger beef ribs pastrami short loin bacon corned beef turducken pork chop. Flank ball tip shoulder short loin, shank prosciutto capicola pig landjaeger fatback. Ribeye beef tongue shankle pastrami, tri-tip pork belly sirloin spare ribs. Jerky chicken tail turducken spare ribs. Ham meatloaf alcatra tri-tip short loin pastrami tenderloin spare ribs cow porchetta chicken short ribs pork cupim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jowl bresaola leberkas, porchetta turkey meatball tail swine ham hock pork belly short loin cow. Tongue brisket shank, tail biltong leberkas fatback swine meatball kevin pork loin short loin sirloin chuck. Spare ribs tri-tip meatball alcatra picanha rump. Leberkas short ribs chicken sirloin strip steak kielbasa. Cow tongue burgdoggen, sirloin bacon capicola meatball turducken landjaeger ball tip leberkas tenderloin pork belly corned beef jerky. Tenderloin pastrami hamburger, alcatra short ribs kielbasa tail ham hock beef ribs drumstick shankle brisket. Capicola jerky porchetta landjaeger.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bacon ipsum dolor amet alcatra corned beef prosciutto frankfurter fatback t-bone.</title>
      <link>https://jamhall.github.io/posts/2017/02/01/bacon</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamhall.github.io/posts/2017/02/01/bacon</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet alcatra corned beef prosciutto frankfurter fatback t-bone, meatball beef ribs ribeye. Flank pork cupim, tri-tip ham shoulder leberkas chicken capicola burgdoggen ham hock ribeye turducken beef ribs. Pork belly filet mignon short ribs shoulder short loin shank. Ground round t-bone pork biltong ball tip turkey shank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alcatra pork belly pork chop pig, fatback capicola tail turkey spare ribs. Strip steak alcatra pig sausage venison. Fatback salami venison, burgdoggen pork chop cow brisket hamburger picanha chicken kielbasa strip steak beef. Rump sirloin tongue shankle. Meatball shankle biltong sausage tail salami picanha kielbasa boudin bresaola porchetta jerky tongue pig pancetta. Prosciutto chicken doner, sausage capicola tenderloin leberkas cow ham ham hock ball tip pork ribeye. Shoulder pancetta t-bone, short ribs turducken kielbasa porchetta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strip steak filet mignon turkey pancetta jerky picanha, short loin tenderloin drumstick pastrami tail tri-tip burgdoggen corned beef shankle. Drumstick pig cupim andouille pork loin. Jowl fatback strip steak, chicken prosciutto pork loin flank leberkas venison andouille meatball meatloaf picanha pig beef ribs. Strip steak brisket pork belly, turducken sausage tenderloin boudin hamburger flank filet mignon kevin biltong pork loin bresaola prosciutto. Chuck bacon alcatra pancetta. T-bone strip steak pig pork belly short loin tenderloin pork chop short ribs andouille turducken chuck prosciutto pork loin bresaola kielbasa. Cow picanha ball tip turducken, prosciutto boudin capicola ham pastrami turkey andouille.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swine capicola tenderloin beef shankle cupim. Sausage beef kielbasa, biltong pork loin brisket jowl ball tip tenderloin beef ribs pork chop drumstick. Beef ribs pancetta andouille picanha jowl flank short ribs bresaola sirloin meatball doner strip steak. Pork ribeye chicken boudin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork loin turkey ground round andouille venison kielbasa beef ribs tri-tip. Meatloaf ball tip turkey pancetta salami pork chop pork loin beef shank. Ham hock venison strip steak, leberkas cow bresaola sirloin landjaeger tail swine pork loin cupim. Short loin meatloaf turducken, kevin rump tail tri-tip porchetta chuck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>https://jamhall.github.io/posts/2017/01/31/hello-world</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamhall.github.io/posts/2017/01/31/hello-world</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello world!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;###### CONFIG
ACCEPTED_HOSTS=&amp;quot;/root/.hag_accepted.conf&amp;quot;
BE_VERBOSE=false

if [ &amp;quot;$UID&amp;quot; -ne 0 ]
then
 echo &amp;quot;Superuser rights required&amp;quot;
 exit 2
fi

genApacheConf(){
 echo -e &amp;quot;# Host ${HOME_DIR}$1/$2 :&amp;quot;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>